看起來你不想繼續盯著
And it looks you wanna break your gaze
你不想要當個縱火的人
you don't wanna be a firestarter
我最近一直要找人輸贏
Well I've been looking for a fight these days
但你只想找個人來謀殺
but you've been looking for another murder
你覺得你能規定我是誰？
Do you think that you can say who I am?
我不覺得你有在專心半點
Well I don't think that you've been paying attention
你覺得你可以全身而退？
Do you think that you can get out without a fight?
你他媽想試，我就給你試
You can try as you damn well please
繼續盯著我，盯著我，噢
keep your eyes on me, eyes on me, oh
而如果你想作弊，我也給你玩
And if you wanna sell out you can hoof da chest
我們的字句相撞
And it's my word against yours
就繼續盯著我，盯著我，噢
so keep your eyes on me, eyes on me, oh
來吧，看著我，瞪著我
Come on and look me and stare me down
我就是不能理解你的緣由你的瘋
I just can't understand your motives and your lunacy
這些傷痕比耳邊風還來的
These scars cut deeper than the whispers had
深痛好多
from behind me
電我，看我
Shock me, watch me
揉的歪七扭八
Twist and turn all around me
你覺得你可以隨便
Do you think that you can get out
安全地脫逃？
without consequence?
你覺得你可以眼神看開？
So you think that you can draw your gaze?
你覺得你可以把我打碎？
So you wanna be the one who breaks me?
我經歷過更遭，而你可以入墳再理解
I've been through worse and you can take that to the grave
入墳
The grave
你覺得你是他媽偉大？
So you think that you're so god damn great?
你覺得你是個神通了嗎？
So you think that you're so powerful now?
就想想看跟我一樣，你會怎樣
Just imagine what it's like be like to be like me
你活看看
Live like me
你他媽想試，我就給你試
You can try as you damn well please
繼續盯著我，盯著我，噢
keep your eyes on me, eyes on me, oh
而如果你想作弊，我也給你玩
And if you wanna sell out you can hoof da chest
我們的字句相撞
And it's my word against yours
就繼續盯著我，盯著我，噢
so keep your eyes on me, eyes on me, oh
來吧，看著我，瞪著我
Come on and look me and stare me down